The biggest thing that people say when they have a busy schedule is that they just can't get their exercise in.
I'm going to give you a few tips on how you might be able to incorporate some exercises to your diet, into your day.
One thing you can do is you can get one of these balls and if you sit at a desk, you can switch out your chair for about an hour and balance on this ball and that helps build your core.
Another thing you can do is you can get on the internet and buys some of these handy little devices, this is a band that you can get some strength training from and use it with your arms and your legs.
Then also this is just a dumbbell that you can stop by any sporting good store and pick some up.
A lot of people say they just don't have time to make it to the gym and that's okay so start parking far away from school, far away from your work not really far but you can go ahead and park maybe an extra ten minutes.
Then you can walk and you'll be getting ten minutes of exercise to work to or to school and ten minutes to walk back.
Think about at the grocery store to or even at the gym.
If you are going to the gym, don't try to find the first parking spot and fight the person for the parking spot.
Simply park in the back of the parking lot and then you'll get maybe five minutes of exercise walking to where ever it might be where you might go.
Remember you can always go on the internet and order many of these simple devices that you can add throughout your day, that way you don't have to spend time going shopping cause we know you're busy.